let questions = [
    {
      "question": `What is the first book of the Old Testament?
        A. Leviticus
        B. Numbers
        C. Genesis
        D. Exodus`,
      "correctAnswer": "C"
    },
    {
      "question": `How would one say goodbye in Spanish?
        A. Hola
        B. Au Revoir
        C. Salir
        D. Adiós`,
      "correctAnswer": "D"
    },
    {
      "question": `What is the French word for 'hat'?
        A.  Casque
        B. Chapeau
        C. Bonnet
        D. Écharpe`,
      "correctAnswer": "B"
    },
    {
      "question": `The New York Times slogan is, 'All the News That's Fit to...';
        A. Digest
        B. Look
        C. Read
        D. Print`,
      "correctAnswer": "D"
    },
    {
      "question": `Which restaurant's mascot is a clown?
        A. Burger King
        B. Sonic
        C. McDonald's
        D. Whataburger`,
      "correctAnswer": "C"
    },
    {
      "question": `Which of the following is the IATA code for Manchester Airport?
        A. MAN
        B. EGLL
        C. LHR
        D. EGCC`,
      "correctAnswer": "A"
    },
    {
      "question": `If you are caught &quot;Goldbricking&quot;, what are you doing wrong?
        A. Stealing
        B. Cheating
        C. Slacking
        D. Smoking`,
      "correctAnswer": "C"
    },
    {
      "question": `Earth is located in which galaxy?
        A. The Black Hole
        B. The Milky Way Galaxy
        C. The Mars Galaxy
        D. The Galaxy Note`,
      "correctAnswer": "B"
    },
    {
      "question": `What are Panama hats made out of?
        A. Silk
        B. Hemp
        C. Flax
        D. Straw`,
      "correctAnswer": "D"
    },
    {
      "question": `What kind of aircraft was developed by Igor Sikorsky in the United States in 1942?
        A. Jet
        B. Space Capsule
        C. Helicopter
        D. Stealth Blimp`,
      "correctAnswer": "C"
    }
  ]